Finding aid for Association for Asian Studies records, 1947-1988
Bentley Historical Library
- Secretariat and other administrative offices
  - 1949-1985, 1970-1979
    - Asian Society, 1973-1977 (Box 22)
    - Asian Folklore Studies Group, 1977-1980 (Box 22)
    - Audits (annual of AAS), 1967-1984; 4 folders (Box 22)
      (some years missing)
    - Bibliography of Asian Studies (Box 22)
      (see "Committees, Publications")
    - Board of Directors
      - Officers Correspondence
        - Presidents
          - Cora DuBois, 1969-1971 (Box 22)
          - C. Martin Wilbur, 1969-1972 (Box 22)
          - Robert E. Ward, 1971-1973 (Box 22)
          - Ping-ti Ho, 1975-1976 (Box 22)
          - Marius B. Jansen, 1976 (Box 22)
        - Secretary-Treasurer
          - General
            - David Joel Steinberg, 1969-1971 (Box 22)
            - Richard L. Park
              - 1971-1972 (Box 22)
              - 1973-1979 (Box 22)
            - L.A. Peter Gosling, 1974-1978 (Box 22)
          - Memos to Board
            - David Joel Steinberg, 1971 (Box 23)
            - Richard L. Park, No. 1-75, 7 folders (Box 23)
            - L.A. Peter Gosling, No. 1-8 (Box 23)
            - Rhoads Murphey, No. 1-12, 2 folders (Box 23)
        - Membership Lists, 1971-1974 (Box 23)
        - Minutes, 1961-1979; 7 folders (Box 23)
        - Summary of Actions, 1970-1971; 1973-1974 (Box 23)
    - Chinese Materials and Research Aids Service Center, 1971 (Box 24)
    - Committees
      - Asian Americans in The Profession, 1971 (Box 24)
      - Asian Law, 1973-1978; 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Automated Bibliographic Controls for East Asian Studies (Box 24)
      - 1967-1974, 8 folders (Box 24)
        (ABC East)
      - Buddhist Studies, 1969-1978 (Box 24)
      - Comparative East Asian Literature, 1970-1977 (Box 24)
      - Concerned Asian Scholars, 1970-1974 (Box 24)
      - Constitutional Revision, 1969-1976; 4 folders (Box 24)
      - Development, 1977 (Box 24)
      - East Asian Libraries, 1971-1980 (Box 24)
      - Economic Relations with Asia, 1977-1981 (Box 24)
      - Educational and Professional Development, 1970-1971 (Box 24)
      - Ethics, 1971 (Box 24)
      - Executive
        - 1960-1972, 3 folders (Box 24)
        - 1973-1978, 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Finance, 1954-1966; 1970; 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Information Control, 1969-1971; 8 folders (Box 25)
      - International Exchange of Persons, 1972-1973 (Box 25)
      - International Liaison, 1969-1974; 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Interuniversity Southeast Asia, 1969 (Box 25)
      - Korean Studies, 1969-1971; 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Language Resources, 1969-1971 (Box 25)
      - Local Arrangements, 1962-1971 (Box 25)
      - Membership, 1970-1975 (Box 25)
      - Nominating, 1970-1981; 3 folders (Box 25)
      - Professional Issues, 1969-1978; 3 folders (Box 26)
      - Professional Needs and Development (Ward Report), 1971-1976; 2 folders (Box 26)
      - Program, 1970-1981; 2 folders (Box 26)
      - Publications
        - General Committee Material (Box 26)
        - Asian Study Thesaurus Proposal, 1975-1976 (Box 26)
        - Computarization, 1975-1980 (Box 26)
        - General, 1970-1976; 7 folders (Box 26)
        - Reports, 1963-1975; 2 folders (Box 26)
        - Publications and Series
          - Asian Studies Professional Review, 1971-1975 (Box 26)
          - Bibliography of Asian Studies
            - Advisory Committee
              - 1969-1973, 2 folders (Box 26)
              - 1974-1977, 2 folders (Box 27)
            - American Council of Learned Societies, 1970 (Box 27)
            - Computerization, 1970; 1972; 2 folders (Box 27)
            - Correspondence, 1970-1983; 4 folders (Box 27)
            - Editors
              - Thein Swe, 1970-1972; 2 folders (Box 27)
              - Frank Shulman, 1970-1972; 2 folders (Box 27)
            - Ford Foundation Grant, 1978 (Box 27)
            - Human Relations Area Files (Hesung C. Koh), 1970-1971; 2 folders (Box 27)
            - Instructional, 1970 (Box 27)
            - ISA, 1970 (Box 27)
            - National Science Foundation, 1969-1970 (Box 27)
            - New Delhi Operations, 1970-1972 (Box 27)
            - Panel Papers, 1971 (Box 27)
            - Reports, 1968-1972; 2 folders (Box 27)
          - Journal of Asian Studies
            - Annual Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 27)
            - Correspondence, 1970-1980; 2 folders (Box 27)
            - Editor
              - John Harrison, 1971-1972; 1975 (Box 27)
              - Harry Harootunian, 1972-1974 (Box 27)
              - Ralph Nicholas, 1975-1977 (Box 27)
              - Editor Search, 1971-1972; 1974-1975; 2 folders (Box 27)
              - Financial, 1972-1980 (Box 27)
              - Thirtieth Anniversary Issue Plans, 1971 (Box 27)
          - Monographs (Box 28)
            - Asia Foundation, 1976-1978 (Box 28)
            - Correspondence, 1971-1978; 2 folders (Box 28)
            - Editor, Paul Wheatley, 1973; 1976 (Box 28)
            - Editor Selection, 1972-1976 (Box 28)
            - Financial, 1971-1978 (Box 28)
            - History of AAS (Hucker), 1971 (Box 28)
            - Reports, 1970-1980 (Box 28)
          - Newsletter, 1961-1977; 3 folders (Box 28)
        - Publications Review, 1974-1975 (Box 28)
        - Research and Development, 1970-1973 (Box 28)
        - Research Materials in Southeast Asia, 1970-1971 (Box 28)
        - Role of Women in Asian Studies, 1970-1978 (Box 28)
        - Scholars of Asian Descent, 1973-1980; 4 folders (Box 28)
        - Secondary Education, 1971-1972 (Box 28)
        - South Asia, 1969 (Box 28)
      - Teaching about Asia, 1972-1980; 5 folders (Box 28)
    - Coordinating Group on International and Area Studies, 1975-1977 (Box 28)
    - DuBois, Cora (Box 29)
      (See "Board of Directors, Officers' Correspondence)
    - Ford Foundation Proposal, 1971; 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Ho Ping-ti (Box 29)
    - Honors: Arthur Hummel Award, 1975-1976 (Box 29)
    - International Congress of Orientalists (abstracts of papers), August 1967; 4 volumes, 1 volume (scrapbook) (Box 29)
    - Jansen, Marius B. (Box 29)
    - Johnson, Carol (Box 29)
      (See "Administrative Officers")
    - Kahin Proposal, 1974-1975 (Box 29)
    - Membership Polls, 1971 (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous, 1969-1979 (Box 29)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1971-1975 (Box 29)
    - Newsletters
      - 1953-1982, 1971-1982; 5 folders (Box 29)
      - 1983-1985 (Box 30)
    - Office of Education, Consultative Conference on International Studies, January 12, 1976 (Box 30)
    - Park, Richard L. (Box 30)
      (See "Board of Directors, Officers' Correspondence")
    - Pearl S. Buck Foundation, 1975 (Box 30)
    - Presidential Commission on Foreign Languages and Area Studies, 1978-1979 (Box 30)
    - Proposed Delegation to Peoples Republic of China, 1972-1974 (Box 30)
    - Regional Councils
      - General, 1970-1976 (Box 30)
      - China and Inner Asia, 1963; 1969-1972; 3 folders (Box 30)
      - Northeast Asia, 1970-1971 (Box 30)
      - South Asia, 1971-1973 (Box 30)
      - Southeast Asia, 1969-1971 (Box 30)
    - Staff Photographs, circa 1972 (Box 30)
    - Translation Project Group, 1969-1970 (Box 30)
    - U.S. Department of ..., 1975; 1978 (Box 30)
    - U.S.-Japan Educational Exchange Program, 1975-1976 (Box 30)
    - Vietnam Studies Coordinating Group, 1971-1972 (Box 30)
    - Vitaly, Rubin (Dissident Soviet Scholar), 1973-1976 (Box 30)
    - Ward, Robert E. (Box 30)
      (see "Board of Directors, Officers' Correspondence")
    - Wilbur, C. Martin (Box 30)
  - General Subjects and Grants, 1951-1983
    - General Subjects
      - Articles by David Steinberg, 1965-1968 (Box 42)
      - Board of Directors minutes, 1982-1984 (Box 42)
      - Chinese publications, 1952-1954; 2 folders (Box 42)
      - Correspondence, 1983-1984; 2 folders (Box 42)
      - Council on Library Resources, 1980-1981 (Box 42)
      - Executive Committee minutes, 1963; 1980; 1982-1984 (Box 42)
      - External research correspondence, 1951 (Box 42)
      - External research reports, 1952 (Box 42)
      - Institution on Current World Affairs, 1966 (Box 42)
      - Membership Committee, 1962; 1964 (Box 42)
      - Membership rosters, 1962-1968 (Box 42)
      - Memorial for Richard L. Park, 1982 (Box 42)
      - Reports on the research of members, 1951; 7 folders (Box 42)
      - Steinberg (David) correspondence, 1966-1969; 1971-1973 (Box 42)
    - Grant files
      - Asia Foundation Travel Grants, 1980 (Box 42)
      - Association of Organization for Korean Studies, 1975 (Box 42)
      - CORMOSEA Developmental proposal, 1970-1973 (Box 42)
      - CORMOSEA Project, 1978-1981; 1983-1984 (Box 42)
      - CORMOSEA Proposal for Vietnam Studies, 1970-1972 (Box 42)
      - Ford Foundation Grants
        - Awards, 1965; 1970-1971; 1975; 1977; 1979; 8 folders (Box 43)
          (The folders are arranged by date of awards with related post-dated items included)
        - Bibliography on Women in South Asia, 1978; 1983 (Box 43)
        - CORMOSEA Development Proposal, 1970-1973 (Box 43)
        - Correspondence, 1971-1976; 4 folders (Box 43)
        - Nepal Studies, 1972-1976 (Box 43)
        - Proposals, 1971; 1974; 1978-1979; 7 folders (Box 43)
        - Proposal ballots, 1978 (Box 43)
      - Japanese-United States Friendship Commission: Travel Grants, 1981-1982; 3 folders (Box 44)
      - Luce Foundation, 1979-1981 (Box 44)
      - McGregor Fund, 1969; 1971 (Box 44)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities
        - Annotated Bibliography of Research Literature on Traditional Chinese Fiction, 1975-1980; 4 folders (Box 44)
        - Bibliography of Asian Studies, 1977-1979; 1980-1982; 2 folders (Box 44)
        - CORMOSEA Proposal, 1983-1985 (Box 44)
        - Russian Studies of Modern China, 1976-1977 (Box 44)
        - Southeast Asia Research Tools Project, 1977-1978; 1980; 1983; 2 folders (Box 44)
        - Taiwan History Studies, 1978-1981 (Box 44)
      - Philippine Group Proposal for Foreign Studies Extension Program, 1969 (Box 45)
      - Proposal for Cross Fertilization of the Social Sciences, 1974-1975 (Box 45)
      - Rockefeller Fund for the Far Eastern Language Book Project, 1948-1951 (Box 45)
      - Title VI Funding, 1972-1973; 2 folders (Box 45)
      - Toyota Grant, 1978; 1981-1983; 2 folders (Box 45)
  - General Subjects and Grants, 1952-1989
    - General Subject Files
      - Administrative Office Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 47)
      - Annual Business Meeting, 1973; 1974 (Box 47)
      - Board of Directors Minutes, 1972-1975; 1977; 1979-1985; 12 folders (Box 47)
      - Constitution and Bylaws, 1982; 1988 (Box 47)
      - Doctoral Dissertations on Asia
        - Correspondence
          - 1952-1953 (Box 47)
            (Harrison Project)
          - 1974-1977, 2 folders (Box 47)
        - Publications (Box 48)
      - Executive Committee Minutes, 1976-1985; 10 folders (Box 48)
      - Nominating Committee
        - Election, 1982 (Box 48)
        - Election, 1986 (Box 48)
      - Office of the Secretary-Treasurer
        - Annual Report, 1977-1986 (Box 48)
        - Correspondence, 1984-1986; 2 folders (Box 48)
      - Annual Report, 1980; 1981 (Box 48)
    - Grant Files
      - List of Grants Received, 1970-1989 (Box 48)
      - Exxon Education Foundation, 1983 (Box 48)
      - Ford Foundation
        - Grant No. 820-0709 (Box 48)
        - Grant No. 710-0559C, 3 folders (Box 48)
      - Japan United States Friendship Commission
        - Grant No. 78-33, 1978-1979 (Box 48)
        - Grant No. 79-47, 1979-1980 (Box 48)
        - Grant Nos. 80-4,80-48,81-65, 1980-1982 (Box 48)
      - Michigan Council for the Humanities
        - Grant No. M120-84, 1985 (Box 48)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities
        - Grant No. CR20007-1842-81, 1980-1983 (Box 49)
        - Grant No. RC20285-82, 1982-1983 (Box 49)
        - Grant No. RC20694-83, 1983 (Box 49)
- Regional Councils
  The Regional Councils series is further divided by name of the individual organization. These are the China and Inner Asia Regional Council; the Northeast Asia Regional Council: the South/Asia Regional Council; and the Southeast Asia Regional Council. Each council's files are arranged into three sub-subseries: Topical Files, Studies Groups and Committees, and Regional Council Affiliates. They records document the council's relationships with the Association secretariat as well as internal council concerns and include correspondence, activity reports, records of the sub-committees, council meeting minutes and other records, and newsletters.
  - China and Inner Asia Regional Council (CIARC)
    - Topical Files, 1961-1980
      - B. Bartlett: Ching Archives, 1976 (Box 31)
      - Budget, 1971-1976 (Box 31)
      - China Abstracts, 1972 (Box 31)
      - Chinese/English Translation Assistance-(Ceta), 1971 (Box 31)
      - Ching-Shih wcu-t'i (Newsletter), 1975-1977 (Box 31)
      - Conference on Chinese Oral and Performing Literature (chinoperl), 1973-1975 (Box 31)
      - Cmrasc, Inc., Dissolution Papers, 1974 (Box 31)
      - Correspondence, 1971-1976 (Box 31)
      - Correspondence, 1975-1980 (Box 31)
      - Correspondence and memos, 1971-1975 (Box 31)
      - Council meeting, November 30, 1979 (Box 31)
      - General, 1969-1975 (Box 31)
      - Minutes, 1970-1974 (Box 31)
      - Minutes and reports
        - 1975-1977 (Box 31)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 31)
      - Society for Study of Chinese Religions Correspondence and newsletters, 1975-1978 (Box 31)
      - State of the Field reports Article, 1978 (Box 31)
      - Structure, annual and financial reports, 1970-1973 (Box 31)
      - Studies Groups and Committees, 1970-1980
        - Developmental Committee on Inner Asia
          - 1973-1976 (Box 31)
          - Teaching aid, 1975-1976 (Box 31)
      - Committee for Taiwan Historical Studies (Box 31)
      - Correspondence and reports, 1974-1980 (Box 31)
      - Committee on East Asian Libraries, 1974-1976 (Box 31)
      - Comparative East Asian Literature Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 31)
      - Ming Biographical History Project Committee
        - 1970-1975 (Box 31)
        - Annual reports and grants, 1961-1969 (Box 31)
        - Budget, 1970-1975 (Box 31)
        - Ming Studies Newsletter, 1975-1976 (Box 31)
      - Regional Council Affiliates Society for Study of Pre-Han China, 1974-1977 (Box 31)
    - Topical Files, 1971-1980
      - American Council of Learned Societies, 1976-1979 (Box 45)
      - Budget, 1976-1978 (Box 45)
      - Committee on Elementary and Secondary Education, 1975 (Box 45)
      - Committee on Professional Needs and Development, 1975 (Box 45)
      - Committee on Professional Principles, 1975-1976; 1978 (Box 45)
      - Committee on the Role of Women in Asia Studies, 1976; 1978 (Box 45)
      - Committee on the Studies of Chinese Cultures, 1972 (Box 45)
      - Committee for the Study of Chinese Religions, 1975-1976 (Box 45)
      - Committee for Taiwan Historical Studies, 1972-1975; 1978-1979 (Box 45)
      - Conference on Sino-Tibetan Languages and Linguistics, 1975 (Box 45)
      - Conference on Social Control and Deviance (The Wilson Report), 1975 (Box 45)
      - Council of Regional Conferences, 1977 (Box 45)
      - Correspondence, 1971-1980; 5 folders (Box 45)
      - Developmental Committee on Inner Asia, 1973-1977; 1980 (Box 45)
      - Ford Foundation Grant reports, 1974-1977 (Box 45)
      - Functions and purposes of the CIARC, 1971-1973; 1976 (Box 45)
      - Funding, 1973-1975 (Box 45)
      - Future of Chinese Studies, 1971-1972; 2 folders (Box 46)
      - Financial report, 1975 (Box 46)
      - Haupen Scholarship, 1974-1975 (Box 46)
      - Indonesian treasures retrieved, 1976 (Box 46)
      - Journal of Asian Studies, 1972; 1974; 1978 (Box 46)
      - Leban Proposal, 1974 (Box 46)
      - Massey Study on Language Competence of Americans, 1972-1975 (Box 46)
      - Meetings of the CIARC, 1971-1977; 7 folders (Box 46)
      - Membership, 1972-1977 (Box 46)
      - Minutes of the CIARC meetings, 1971-1973; 1974 (Box 46)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1974; 2 folders (Box 46)
      - Nominations to AAS offices, 1977-1978 (Box 46)
      - Nominations to CIARC offices, 1972-1977 (Box 46)
      - Oksenberg report on Chinese studies in the, 1970s; 1972 (Box 46)
      - Panel discussion of the Lambert Report, 1973 (Box 46)
      - Program Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 46)
      - Proposed delegation to the Peoples Republic of China, 1972; 1975 (Box 46)
      - Regional Conferences of the CIARC, 1974; 1976-1977 (Box 46)
      - Reports from the AAS's annual meeting, 1977; 1979 (Box 46)
      - Russian studies on modern China, 1976-1977 (Box 46)
      - Saigon political prisoners referendum, 1973 (Box 46)
      - State of the Field papers, 1977-1979; 3 folders (Box 47)
      - Student representatives to the CIARC, 1971-1972 (Box 47)
      - Teaching aids for the Study of Inner Asia, no. 1-7, 1975; 2 folders (Box 47)
      - University Service Center, 1977-1978 (Box 47)
      - Ward Report on Professional Needs and Development, 1975-1976 (Box 47)
  - Northeast Asia Regional Council (NEARC), 1970-1986
    - Topical Files, 1970-1980
      - Annual reports and disbursement summaries, 1971-1979 (Box 32)
      - Correspondence, 1971-1977 (Box 32)
      - Meeting minutes, 1970-1980 (Box 32)
      - Memorandums, 1972-1974 (Box 32)
      - Proposals and reports, 1970-1980 (Box 32)
    - Studies Groups arid Area Committees, 1970-1975
      - Committee on Korean Studies
        - Annual and Topical reports, 1970-1974 (Box 32)
        - Correspondence, meetings and proposals, 1972-1975 (Box 32)
      - Regional Council Affiliates, 1970-1977
        - Association of Teachers of Japanese Correspondence and reports, 1970-1977 (Box 32)
    - Grants Received from Japan United States Friendship Council
      - Grant No. 78-34, 1978-1979 (Box 49)
      - Grant No. 79-42, 1979-1980 (Box 49)
      - Grant No. 80-70, 1980-1981 (Box 49)
      - Grant No. 81-68, 1981-1982 (Box 49)
      - Grant No. 82-74, 1983-1984 (Box 49)
      - Grant No. 84-37, 1983-1984 (Box 49)
      - Grant No. 85-06, 1984-1985 (Box 49)
      - Grant No. 86-41, 1986 (Box 49)
  - South/Asia Regional Council (SARC), 1955-1978
    South/Asia Regional Council (SARC) files are of note for a survey of Asian Studies programs in universities throughout the nation, and for the records of the Temporary Committee of Displaced Scholars, which dealt with the consequences the Pakistani civil war and the foundation of the independent nation of Bangladesh. SARC lacks a Regional Council Affiliate series.
    - Topical Files, 1968-1979
      - AAS-SARC Annual Reports
        - 1968-1970 (Box 32)
        - 1970-1971 (Box 32)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 32)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 32)
      - AAS and Ford Annual Report, 1976 (Box 32)
      - AAS Executive Board/SARC Relations and Regional Council Guidelines, 1971 (Box 32)
      - Ad hoc Committees on
        - Outreach Education, 1977 (Box 32)
        - Pakistan Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 32)
        - Priorities, 1971-1972 (Box 32)
      - American Institute of Indian Studies Scholarship Information, 1969-1971 (Box 32)
      - Annual Meeting
        - 1971 (Box 32)
        - 1973 (Box 32)
      - Annual Reports
        - 1976 (Box 32)
        - 1977 (Box 32)
        - 1978 (Box 32)
        - 1979 (Box 32)
      - Bhubaneswar Conference, 1976 (Box 32)
      - Center Directors Ad hoc Steering Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 32)
      - Central Institute of Indian Languages, 1969-1971 (Box 32)
      - Chairmen of SARC
        - Correspondence
          - 1974-1977 (Box 32)
          - 1977-1978 (Box 32)
        - Trip to India
          - John Broomfield, 1969-1970 (Box 32)
          - Joe Elder, 1971 (Box 32)
      - Committee of Concerned Asian Scholars, 1969-1970 (Box 32)
      - Committee on Asian Law, 1970 (Box 32)
      - Committee on Scholars and Schools Final Report to SARC, 1972 (Box 32)
      - Committee on South Asian Libraries and Documentation (CONSALD)
        - 1969-1980 (Box 32)
        - Annual Report, 1976 (Box 32)
        - Newsletter, 1978-1979 (Box 32)
      - Conferences
        - 1973 (Box 32)
        - 1975 (Box 32)
      - Conference on kinship and history, 1973 (Box 32)
      - Correspondence
        - 1970-1975 (scattered) (Box 32)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 32)
      - Council for Intercultural Studies and Programs, 1974-1975 (Box 32)
      - Data Bank Proposal, 1970-1973 (Box 32)
      - Development Specialists Liaison Subcommittee, 1968-1970 (Box 33)
      - East Pakistan Crisis, Press Conference, December, 1971 (Box 33)
      - Executive Committee and Ford, 1976 (Box 33)
      - Fall Conference-letter to Committees re: planning, 1973 (Box 33)
      - Ford Foundation
        - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 33)
        - Grants
          - No. 68-485, 1968-1971 (Box 33)
          - No. 619-7220, 1971-1972 (Box 33)
          - No. 690-0722, 1969-1972 (Box 33)
          - No. 710-0559, 1971-1975 (Box 33)
          - No. 710-0559A, 1973 (Box 33)
          - No. 710-0559B, 1975 (Box 33)
        - Proposal to, 1974 (Box 33)
        - Report and publications, 1976 (Box 33)
        - Tax memo, 1970 (Box 33)
      - Gandhi Centennial Committee, 1969-1971 (Box 33)
      - Ghalib Centenary Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 33)
      - Historical Atlas project, 1969-1970 (Box 33)
      - History and structure, 1968-1972 (Box 33)
      - Kinship and Caste in India: Oster proposal to SARC, 1975 (Box 33)
      - Language and Area Studies Survey, 1974 (Box 33)
      - Language testing and proficiency, 1973 (Box 33)
      - Meeting
        - 1972 (Box 33)
        - 1974 (Box 33)
        - 1975 (Box 33)
        - 1976 (Box 33)
        - 1977 (Box 33)
        - 1978 (Box 33)
      - Minutes
        - 1969 (Box 33)
        - 1970 (Box 33)
        - 1971 (Box 33)
        - 1972 (Box 33)
        - 1973 (Box 33)
        - 1974 (Box 33)
        - 1975 (Box 33)
        - 1976 (Box 33)
        - 1978-1980 (Box 33)
      - Newsletter, 1955-1975 (Box 33)
      - Nominating committee, 1973 (Box 33)
      - North India Studies Association, 1974-1976 (Box 33)
      - Overseas South Asia Activity Survey, 1974 (Box 33)
      - Program Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 33)
      - Reports, 1969-1977 (Box 33)
      - SARC: Report to AAS
        - 1972-1973 (Box 33)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 33)
      - South Asia Microform Project (SAMP), 1969-1977 (Box 33)
      - Temporary Committee for Displaced Scholars (Bangladesh)
        - Applications, 1972; 2 folders (Box 34)
        - Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 34)
        - History, Draft proposals, 1971 (Box 34)
        - Meetings
          - July, 1971 (Box 34)
          - September, 1971 (Box 34)
          - October, 1971 (Box 34)
        - Report to Ford, 1971; 1973 (Box 34)
        - Transcript of discussion, 1973 (Box 34)
      - United States Educational Foundation in India: Correspondence and Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 34)
      - University Curricula
        - American University (Box 34)
        - California State College, Hayward (Box 34)
        - California (University of) Berkeley (Box 34)
        - Chicago (University of) (Box 34)
        - Claremont Graduate School (Box 34)
        - Columbia University (Box 34)
        - Cornell University (Box 34)
        - Davidson College (Box 34)
        - Duke University (Box 34)
        - Illinois (University of) (Box 34)
        - Kansas State University (Box 34)
        - Michigan State University (Box 34)
        - Michigan (University of) (Box 34)
        - Minnesota (University of) (Box 34)
        - Missouri (University of) (Box 34)
        - Oakland University (Box 34)
        - Pennsylvania (University of) (Box 34)
        - Rochester (University of) (Box 34)
        - Texas (University of) (Box 34)
        - Virginia (University of) (Box 34)